<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on New England Hedgehogs</title>
    <link>https://newenglandhedgehogs.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on New England Hedgehogs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 22:45:33 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newenglandhedgehogs.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are Hedgehogs Legal Near Me?</title>
      <link>https://newenglandhedgehogs.com/post/are-hedgehogs-legal-near-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 22:45:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newenglandhedgehogs.com/post/are-hedgehogs-legal-near-me/</guid>
      <description>Are Hedgehogs Legal Near Me? If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this from New England, then you&amp;rsquo;re all set, because hedgehogs are legal everywhere in New England. Unfortunately, other regions aren&amp;rsquo;t so lucky, and some states have it out for these lovable little prickleballs!
A Southern New Hampshire-based hedgehog breeder has a great resource outlining everywhere in the United States where hedgehogs are legal and illegal:
 Are Hedgehogs Legal in My State?  Some states that have made hedgehogs illegal claim that hedgehogs could become an invasive species (They won&amp;rsquo;t — hedgehogs can&amp;rsquo;t survive outdoors in North American climates that are much colder than the hot African climates that they thrive in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Credits</title>
      <link>https://newenglandhedgehogs.com/post/website-credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 10:45:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newenglandhedgehogs.com/post/website-credits/</guid>
      <description>Photography Many thanks to the following folks who have allowed us to use their cute photos and beautiful graphics!
 Hamor Hollow Hedgehogs — USDA-licensed hedgehog breeder located in Southern New Hampshire Hamor Photography — Lifestyle, event, urban, and tech photography in Southern New Hampshire  Stock Images Public Domain (CC0) License  Hedgehog SVG Vector 34 (212050) from SVG Repo  Website Theme  Hugo Novela by Forestry  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
